Lazy Game Food Reviews
懒人游戏美食评测
One onion
先来个洋葱
We need the one half for this
用一半就好
Yeee!
好极了！
Going to be sweating the onions so we need just a little bit of olive oil
要把洋葱脱水的话，可以加点橄榄油
A hot pot
烫热锅底
There we go...
就是这样......
Just cover it up, let it do its thing for about 5 minutes
把锅盖盖上，焖五分钟
Oh yeah. That is what I want
好极了，就是这样
Just like slightly seared, and nice and soft
稍微焦了一点，但是整个很软:-)
Oh, thats cool. I am just going to add about half a teaspoon of Garam Masala: Indian Spices.
哦，已经凉下来了。我现在要加半勺Garam Masala，一种印度香料
Mmmm.... That smells.... REEEALLLY GOOOOD!!!!
嗯~闻上去......真是沁人心脾:-)
I gonna have a bit of a laziness streak.
今天咱犯个懒来个简单的
I am going to go with this "Jack Daniels Pulled Chicken".
咱们今儿吃"Jack Daniels Pulled Chicken（手撕鸡）"
It is already cooked, and seasoned. You just heat it up for a few minutes and...
这个已经弄熟了，而且调完味了，仅需加热几分钟然后
its ready to go
就可以吃啦
And yeah, its ermm. its a lot more uh... tasty than it looks.
当然，这个看上去......美食不可貌相
This is not a very appetising little bag of stuff
这包东西看上去真是不提胃口
While That's Going...
在加热的同时呢
Just gonna use about an 8 inch white roll.
咱处理这个8吋长的白面包
注：在英美，半磅以上（约合四两半）的面包称为bread，在此之下的称为roll
Not going to cut it all the way through. I actually want that little crevice in there.
不一定非得一刀下去，在这留条缝隙挺好
Yeahh... Some good chicken
然后是......放点好吃的鸡肉
I worked so hard on it
这玩意我没少折腾
I was gonna put some spinach on here, but I ran out
我想放点菠菜叶，可惜我用完了
So I am just gonna go ahead with the pickles anyway.
所以我就在这里放点酸黄瓜吧
Oh man...
天啊......
Oh yes.
:-)
Ah yeah, I don't even need chips today.
哈，今天我都没必要放薯片了:-)
I don't even need any chips or anything
今天我都不需要放薯片之类的了
I don't need cheese, I would have liked the spinach,
奶酪也不要了，要有菠菜就更好了
But, Don't need cheese.
但是，我不需要奶酪
Delightfully messy
好吃得都掉渣了:-|
Thats pretty much all I got to say
要我说，这就很好
It's very sweet and sour kinda savory chicken onions and little pickle.
酸甜正好，鸡肉和洋葱下饭，酸黄瓜开胃
This is simple and extremely tasty and I hope you are hungry now, because I am.
今天的美味好做又好吃。希望大家馋了，因为我馋了
Mmm..........
本视频由SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR发布于2017.2.19